<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Abhivyanjana@2015</string>
    <string name="hello_world">SANAM PURI</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="abhivyanjan">\nAbhivyanjana is the annual techn-o-cultural fest of the Gautam Buddha University. Every year Abhivyanjana is held for a span of two days. The two days are packed with various cultural and technical events.

It is an interactive ground for the dynamic youth.Every year, students from Gautam Buddha University attend this technical extravaganza, in an atmosphere which makes them learn and unlearn through an application-oriented approach. It acts as a platform for them to showcase their technological and engineering prowess and nourishes growing scientific talent.

Students get together to celebrate the spirit of life by participating in various cultural, technical and social events in various dimensions of performing arts. There are solo and group performances like Music (Instrumental and Vocal), Dancing, Painting, Collage Making, Paper Presentation, Debate, Model Making, Robotic Competition, Skits, Drama, etc.</string>
    <string name="scavenger"><b>SCAVENGER HUNT\n
\n\n\nTime:02:00 p.m. to 03:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:Sarovar\n
\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
A scavenger hunt is a game in which the organizers prepare a list defining specific items, which the participants , individuals or teams , seek to gather all items on the list, usually without purchasing them ,or perform tasks or take photographs of the items, as specified. The goal is usually to be the first to complete the list, although in a variation on the game players can also be challenged to complete the tasks on the list in the most creative manner.\n

\n\n\n
CONTACT
ADITYA PANWAR
adi.caddy@gmail.com
7838665288</b>
</string>
    <string name="pleasuretreasure"><b>PLEASURE TREASURE\n

\n\n\n\nTime : 09:00 a.m. to 11:00 a.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue : Buddha Statue Stairs\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  A treasure hunt is a game which can have several teams who try to find hidden articles, locations or places inside the University campus by using a series of clues to find the ultimate reward\n
\n\n\n
\n\n\nCONTACT
AparnaGangwar : g.aparna.g@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="paintgrenade">\n<b>PAINT GRENADE\n

\n\n\nTime : 10:00 a.m. to 11:00 a.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue : Sarovar\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  This is a fun activity that would be played between teams of 5 members each. Baloons filled with washable paint is the weapon whereas the opponents are the target. The mission is to capture the flag at each level.\n

 \n
\n\n\nCONTACT\n
Kartik Agarwal : kartik8695@gmail.com
9560773199 </b>
</string>
    <string name="sketchthescinerio">\n<b>SKETCH THE SCENARIO\n

\n\n\n\Time : 11:00 a.m. to 12:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\Venue : Sarovar\n
\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  The beauty is in the eyes of the viewer, so, the participant can choose a view from the university campus and sketch/paint the same.
\n
 \n
\n\n\n
        CONTACT\n
AayushChauhan : aayushcool95@gmail.com
9911417757</b>
</string>
    <string name="gottahangemall">\n<b>GOTTA HANG EM ALL\n

\n\n\n\nTime : 10:00 a.m. to 11:00 a.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue : Sarovar\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  GOTTA HANG EM ALL, as the name suggest, the teams will create a hanging art piece from the material given. A specific theme will be given to the teams. The main focus is on enhancing the ideas of an individual and using the material in a creative way.
\n\n
CONTACT\n
Shashank Bhatt : shashank.vic@gmail.com
8506090220</b>
</string>
    <string name="embossit">\n<b>EMBOSS IT\n

\n\n\nTime : 2:00 p.m. to 3:30 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue : Sarovar\n
DESCRIPTION\n
•  Emboss it is an activity in which a painting is made by embossing the material.In this activity you have make painting on the cardboard by making a mixture of calcium carbonate/chalk powder and oil by embossing it through paper cone or poly cone.

\n.
\n\n\nCONTACT\n
rashmi - rashmisagar83@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="papershaper">\n<b>Paper shaper\n
\n\n\n\nTime : 10:00 a.m. to 11:00 a.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue : Sarovar\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  Paper shaper is a game based activity in which you have to make sculptures from old newspapers.
. You have to use newspapers ,water and glue to make sculptures in the most attractive way.
\nRULES and REGULATIONS\n
1. Each team consists of maximum 2 members.
2. Only first 15 teams will be there.
3. News papers will be provided to each team.\n
\n\n\nCONTACT\n
ArchanaVerma : archanaverma024@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="eggpainting">
    \n<b>Egg Painting\n

   \n\n\n\n Time : 04:30 p.m. to 05:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
    \n\n\n\nVenue : Sarovar\n
    \n\n\DESCRIPTION\n
    •  “HUMPTY DUMPTY SAT ON A WALL PAINT ME CAREFULLY I’M SO SMALL” Humpty and dumpty the eggs have a message for you, they requests for painting them carefully and attractive so that they can impress their girlfriends.

    \n\n
    \n\n\nCONTACT\n
    Rahul garg : 11ice087@gmail.com
    mobile number : 8800987846</b>
</string>
    <string name="wrapperwarriors">\n<b> Wrapper warriors\n

    \n\n\n\n\nTime : 03:00p.m. to 04:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
   \n\n\n\n\n Venue : Sarovar\n
    \n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
    •  You have to usechips wrappers,toffee wrappers etc to make a theme based poster.

    \n\n
    \n\n\nCONTACT\n
    Arushi Sharma arushi241993@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="rangoli">\n<b>RANGOLI COMPETITION\n
\n\n\nTime:12:30 p.m. to 02:00 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:Sarovar\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
Rangoli is a fabulous hand drawing art of India;
it is a way to express imagination.
So, show your creativity and take part in “rangoli competition”.
\n\n
\n\n\nCONTACT\n
Ayushi Bhati
ayushibhati6@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="gbuin60sec">\n<b>GBU IN 60 SECONDS\n

\n\n\nTime : 10:30 a.m. to 11:30 a.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue : SOM Auditorium\n
\n\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  Gautam Buddha University is a very beautiful and photogenic place. With some latest movies being shot here, it has proved to be Bollywood’s hot favorite too. GBU in 60 seconds is a competition about expressions, enjoyment and what and difference it makes to be in GBU.

\n

\n\n\nCONTACT\n
AnkurDubey : ankurdubey2211@gmail.com
9910138632</b>
</string>
    <string name="youtubers">	\n<b>YOUTUBERS\n

\n\n\nTime : 11:30 p.m. to 12:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue : SOM Audi\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  You tubing is becoming phenomenal nowadays. Generally, it is a one-person show. Most you tubers are spontaneous, talk about the stuff that matters and that too live. This job is very much challenging and requires them to have detailed knowledge of each and everything for which they go on air. Based on this concept, student would have to make solo or duet videos on various topics. This competition aims to sharpen the presentation skills of students making them more spontaneous and motivating out of the box thinking.
\n1. Superwoman

\n2. Holly shit

\n3. Pretentious Movie Reviews

\n4. Following is a guide to help the students in understanding the concept of YouTubing.


\n\n



\nTHEMES\n
\n1. What I do during exams!
\n2. What if .....?
\n3. Public opinion.
\n4. Movie review.
\n5. Gadget review.
\n6. Ways to propose a girl or boy.
\n\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nAbhinav Singh : abhinav1815@gmail.com
9999375802</b>
</string>
    <string name="killthebeats"><b>\nKILL THE BEATS\n

\n\n\n\nTime:01:00 p.m. to 03:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\nVenue:SOM Auditorium\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  This is a solo dance event. Any one can participate once they have cleared the audition for the respective dance event.\n


\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nSunpreetKaur : sunpreetkaur.1993@gmail.com</b>


</string>
    <string name="debate">
    \n<b>Debate\n

   \n\n\n Time : 11:00 a.m. to 12:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
   \n\n\n\Venue : SOBT Auditorium\n
   \n\n\n\n DESCRIPTION\n
    •  INCLUDES TWO SEPARATE EVENTS based on Language.
    \na)HINDI LANGUAGE
    \nb)ENGLISH LANGUAGE

    \n
    \nCONTACT
    \nAbhishek Kumar : asuknoit@gmail.com
    8744816086</b>
</string>
    <string name="extempore"><b>\nEXTEMPORE\n

\n\n\n\nTime : 2:00 p.m. to 3:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\nVenue : SOM Auditorium\n
\n\n\n\DESCRIPTION\n
•  INCLUDES TWO SEPARATE EVENTS based on Language.
a)HINDI LANGUAGE\n
b)ENGLISH LANGUAGE\n


\nTOPIC : (TOPIC WILL BE PROVIDED ON THE SPOT(EVERY PARTICIPANT WILL BE PROVIDED DIFFERRENT TOPIC)

\n
\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nAshwaniRai : ashwinroorkee123@gmail.com
7838822605</b>
</string>
    <string name="skitcomptition"><b>\nSkit Competition\n
\n\n\nTime:11:00 a.m. to 01:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\nVenue:SOM Auditorium\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
\n•  This is a team event. The maximum no. of the participants in any team can be 15.

\n
\n\n\n\n\nCONTACT
Arpit : arpitkaushik96@gmail.com
9650102405</b>
</string>
    <string name="actonthespot">\n<b>Act on the Spot\n
\n\n\n\nTime:12:30 p.m. to 02:00 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:SOM Auditorium\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  This is a team event.

\n
.
\n\n\nCONTACT

\nAnkit Sharma : ankitsharma300397@gmail.com
7042762262</b>
</string>
    <string name="comedyhour"><b>\nComedy Hour</b>
\n
<b>\n\n\nTime : 3:30 p.m. to 4:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\nVenue : SOBT Auditorium\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  Comedy-Hour needs no introduction as the name says it all. It’s an interactive Event to show your skill of Stand-up comedy. As we all know the skill of making people laugh is considered to be the best and above all other talents so the event aims at extracting the ultimate talent of stand-up comedy and it provides the student a stage to explore their talent.

\n

   \n CONTACT
    \nTarun kumar Bheda : tarunbheda@gmail.com
9650363865</b>
</string>
    <string name="circiutmania"><b>\nCircuit Mania\n
\n\n\nTime : 11:00 a.m. to 1:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue : Electronics Lab, SOICT\n
\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
•  In this world of everlasting competition, Take your knowledge about electronics in your mind also in your hand and show your electronics skills. The students are provided with complex circuits and some optimized amount of related components from which they have to reduce down the circuit to optimized level and then have to patch the circuit with those components on the breadboard in the given period of time.

\nThis event will be conducted in 2 rounds and all the rounds are related to circuit designing on Breadboard/PCB. This impromptu circuit design competition requires the participants to design a specific electronic and electrical application by using the components provided by us.

\n\n\nGuidelines:

\n1. Phase I (Elimination round)
First round will begin with MCQ round in which participants will have to answer problems based on basic engineering questions. Selected participants will step into the next round.
\n2. Phase II (Final round):
\nIn next round questions will be provided along with circuit components where participants will have to join the circuit correctly. All participants will also be asked to mount the circuit on breadboard.

\n

\n\n\nCONTACT
\nDeepak Bhati : deepakgbu1@gmail.com
9560617105</b>
</string>
    <string name="brainfreeze"><b>\nBRAIN FREEZE\n
\n\n\n\nTime : 2:00 p.m. to 3:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\nVenue : SOE Lecture Room\n
\n\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
\n•  Most of us have seen at least a single episode of Jeopardy on television. The format of Brain Freeze is similar in some ways, different in others. There is a host, but rather than three individual players there are five teams of two players each, in total ten players. Teams work together to answer the questions presented, pooling their knowledge base. If each team member comes up with a different answer, they must also be able to work together to choose which answer to submit. Like Jeopardy, there is also an element of wagering, as well as risk, based upon point values and confidence in a specific category. Brain Freeze is both strategy based and knowledge based, in other words.

\nParticipants will have to pass several rounds which would include quiz( preliminary qualifying round),solve Rubik’s cube etc. Last 5 teams will battle it out in a final round to win the competition.

\n

\nTeam Specifications:

\n1. Max team size: 2 members

\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nVidya Ritik : vidyaritik@gmail.com
\n9958915128</b>
</string>
    <string name="canyoumimic"><b>\nCAN YOU MIMIC ?</b>\n
<b>\n\n\nTime:03:30 p.m. to 04:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:Buddha Statue Stairs\n
DESCRIPTION\n
\nIn this event it’s a game in which the normal game of Dumbcharades (enacting the name of a movie to the team for winning) is modified a bit
A phrase would be given to the participant and you have to enact it using props so that your team can guess the exact phrase. The phrase could be any famous dialogue from a movie or tag line of any brand’s advertisement.
\n
\nCONTACT
        Yaman:08800341061</b>
</string>
    <string name="professionalwriting"><b>\nPROFESSIONAL WRITING\n
\n\n\n\nTime : 04:30 p.m. to 05:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\nVenue : LH-102 , SOM\n
\n\n\n\DESCRIPTION\n
\n • Introduction
\nThe aim of this event is to generate more awareness about the importance of knowing how to write professional letters, reports, slogans, etc.
\nThe event will be divided into three categories of sub-events:
\n- Ad-Writing: where the students will be given a product for which they’ll have to frame a one/two-liner ad slogan.
\n- Report Writing: a general topic will be given and the participants would have to write a professional report on it.
\n- Response Letter Writing: a formal letter would have to be written on a topic given on the spot.


\n• Problem statement
\nThe writings should strictly be in a very formal/professional manner.

\n


\n
\nCONTACT
\nDevisha Singh : singhdevisha16@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="literarywriting"><b>\nLITERARY WRITING\n
\n\n\n\nTime:01:00 p.m. to 02:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\nVenue:LH102 , SOM\n
\n\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n</b>
\nIntroduction:- The mission of the literary writing is to encourage emerging writers and promote literary excellence through its competition structure. This event is divided into two subcategories:-
\na) STORY WRITING/NARRATION: Narration is story writing and then telling. In many ways it is the easiest kind of writing because it comes so naturally to most people. Practically everyone enjoys telling and hearing stories. Short stories, novels, personal narratives are all examples of narrative writing.
\nb) LITERARY CRITISICM:- Literary criticism is an extension of the social activity of interpreting. One reader writes down his or her views on what a particular work of literature means so that others can respond to that interpretation. The critic’s specific purpose may be to make volume judgement on a work , to explain his or her interpretation of the work, or to provide other readers with relevant historical or biographical information . The critics general purpose is to enrich the reader’s understanding of the literary work.
\nRULES and REGULATIONS
\n1) Narration (Narrative Writing)-

\n•	• 3000 words maximum, the title is not included in the word count
\n•	• Participants may be given a topic at the spot or can be free expression, to write a short story on it.
\n•	• Entries must be entirely the work of the entrant and by submitting you are confirming that the work is your own. Any evidence to the contrary will result in immediate disqualification.
\n•	• Participants are allotted 10 minutes to narrate their stories, but the narration is optional.
\n•	• Maximum no. of participants- 30
\n•	• Participants may write in either Hindi or English Language
\n2) Literary Criticism-

\n•	• Maximum 350-400 words on a short story/poetry/drama
\n•	• Participants are allotted 20 minutes
\n•	• Maximum no. of participants- 30
\nJudging Criteria-

\n•	I. Substance and originality
\n•	II. Clarity, Creativity and Practicality
\n•	III. Writing style, Composition and Organisation
\n•	IV. Language, Grammer and Presentation
\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nSonal Chandra
\nchandrasonal73@gmail.com
9599255804
</string>
    <string name="kavisammelan"><b>\nKAVI SAMMELAN\n
\n\n\n\nTime:03:30 p.m. to 05:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:SOM Auditorium\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
Introduction\n
\nIt aims to promote writing and analytical skills with futuristic approach among university students along with encouraging research, analysis and argument development on the important themes.
\nThe poetry will be written and judged in three categories: satire, contemporary, and comic. All poems presented should fall in one of the following categories.
\n

\n2) Narration (Narrative way)-
\n• Entries must be entirely the work of the entrant and by submitting you are confirming that the work is your own. Any evidence to the plagiarism will result in immediate disqualification.


\nJudging Criteria-
\nI. Substance and originality
\nII. Clarity, Creativity and Practicality
\nIII. Poetry style, way of speaking or unique
\nIV. Public appreciation
\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nPriyank Mishra
\npriyankspd@gmail.com
8826319366</b>
</string>
    <string name="iactive"><b>\nI ACTIVE\n
\n\n\nTime:4:30 p.m. to 05:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:SOBT Auditorium\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
Do you like Cars and Bikes, loves Music and Movies, know your Country and the Products we use, know some science and want to check how fast your mind works , then this quiz is just for you. Get ready to compete with the sharpest and fastest minds with a passion for the business and science world.
\n
\n\n\nCONTACT
\nShivansh Gujral
\nshivanshgujral@gmail.com
9999143272</b>
</string>
    <string name="globaledge"><b>\nGLOBAL EDGE\n
\n\n\nTime:03:00 p.m. to 04:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:SOM Auditorium\n
\n\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
\nWe are living in a globalized world with each individual exposed to information about other nations. Global EDGE is informative and tests your knowledge about other economies. It provides an opportunity to the participants to showcase their skills.
\n
\n\n\n\CONTACT
\nChirag Yadav
\n9873769661
chiragyadav1991@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="melodia"><b>\nMELODIA\n
\n\n\nTime:09:00 a.m. to 11:00 a.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:SOM Auditorium\n
\n\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
\nThis is the hunt for the most versatile singer of the institution. If you’ve got a mesmerizing voice, or the rock star attitude, “Melodía ” gives you the opportunity to steal the show. Come, sing your hearts out, and if you impress the judges, you will own the tag of the voice of GBU.
\n

\n\n\nCONTACT
Nuba Zaidi
zaidinuba@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="shuttercuisine"><b>\nSHUTTER CUISINE\n
\n\n\nTime:12:00 p.m. onwards\n
\n\n\n\nVenue:SOBT Backside\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
\n• In SHUTTER CUISINE, we encourage young and talented photographers to bring forward their talent.
\nPhotographers send their entries and the best entries are felicitated with trophies and certificates.
\n• The participants can submit 3 photographs per theme and each participant cannot select more than 2 themes, i.e., maximum 6 entries per participant.
\n• We would definitely showcase minimum 3 photographs per participants.
\n


\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nMoumita Das
\n11IBT035
moumita.das2093@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="selfiesh"><b>\nSELFIESH\n
\n\n\nTime:12:30 p.m. onwards on February 13th - 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:SOBT Backside\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
\n• In SELFIESH, we encourage young and talented photographers to bring forward their talent of clicking a Selfie. People can send their entries and the best entries are felicitated with trophies and certificates.
\n• The participants can submit 2 per theme and each participant cannot select more than 2 themes, i.e., maximum 6 entries per participant.
\n• We would definitely showcase minimum 3 photographs per participants.
\n
\n\n\n\CONTACT
\nHimanshu Tomar
9818072029
himanshutomar24@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="linefollower"><b>\nLINE FOLLOWER\n
\n\n\nTime:11:00 a.m. to 01:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:SOICT Backside\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
The Line follower robot is a mobile machine that can detect and follow the line drawn on the floor. Generally, the path is predefined and can be visible like a black line on a white surface with a high contrasted colour. Participants should have to complete the paths as per rules and regulation. Event is divided in two rounds. Participants who completed each round in less time with minimum faults will be declared as a winner.
\nSPECFICATION
\nMachine Specifications:
\n• The Robot must be strictly autonomous. \n• The width of the black (no white line) will be less than 5cm \n• Dimensions of the Robot should be less than 20cm*20cm*20cm (l x b x h)\n • A power supply should be of maximum 12-15 V.
\nArena specifications:
\n• The arena is made up on the white cartridge sheet with black line of around 2-3 cm . \n• The course line (turns) may have acute, obtuse and right angles curves \n• The schematic design of the arena will be shown to the participants a day before the event.
\nRULES and REGULATIONS
\n•	The Robot has to follow the black line on white background and complete the track in least possible time. Maximum 3 touches will be allowed for each round. (each touch contains 5 sec penalty.)
\n•	Maximum Four Participants are allowed in a team.
\n•	Team members can be from different colleges.
\n•	If the machine remains immobile for respectable time then marking will be as per the judges discretion.

\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nUtkarsh Srivastava
11/IEC/117
+91-8826363547
srivastava92utkarsh@gmail.com</b>
</string>
    <string name="gamingfiesta"><b>\nGAMING FIESTA\n

\n\n\nTime : 08:00 a.m. to 01:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\nVenue : Computer Lab II , SOM\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
\n•  Gaming Fiesta is a gaming event in which participants will have a choice of two games:

\n• Counter Strike 1.6
\n• Fifa 14
\n

\n


\nGame Format:
\nCompetition Method:	5 vs. 5
\nPlayers:	10 total (5 on each team)
\nRounds:	20 rounds for regulation play
\nMax Rounds Format:	10 rounds as Offense, and 10 rounds as Defense per team until the victory condition is met
\nVictory Condition:	The first team to win 11 rounds in regulation.
\nBuytime:	20 seconds
\nStartmoney:	$800 for regulation play
\nFreezetime:	15 seconds
\n
\nSide Selection:
\n
\n• By knife round / coin toss
\n
\nThere will be only one trophy for the teams winning 1st , 2nd and 3rd position .
\n
\n
\nFifa 14:
\nAll matches must be played in accordance with FIFA Laws of the Game, except as specifically modified as follows in the tournament rules:
\n1. Game Mode
\nThe event will be a knockout tournament.
\nFor ease of use all games will be played in “Friendly” mode. After the game is finished, the computers will be guided back to the Home Screen and a new ‘Friendly” will be selected.
\n2. Picking Teams
\nEvery player is allowed to pick their preferred team. Teams can be picked before the start of the game. Players are allowed to usemultiple teams throughout the tournament as they please. It is accepted to have the same teams play against each other (e.g.Barcelona vs Barcelona).In that case, the ‘away’ player will have to pick the Away Jersey for that team. In general, ‘away’ players are responsiblefor picking the jersey that does not resemble the home team jersey.
\n3. Score Recording
\nThe scores will be reported to the score table by both players after the game. Marshalls will also record scores to make sure allscores are reported fairly.
\n4. Game Length
\nPrelim rounds will be of 2 X 4minute halves.
\nSucceeding rounds will be of 2 X 5minute halves.
\nThe final round will be of 2X6 minutes.

\nThere will be no more than 45 seconds for setting the starting line up and the half timechanges (45 seconds for each). Field marshals will check on the times and make sure the games are played fairly.


\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nManas Malhotra (CS) : manas_12rocks@yahoo.com
\n8130934177
\nHriday Taneja (FIFA) : 8882074441</b>
</string>
    <string name="woodencar"><b>\nWOODEN CAR\n
\n\n\nTime:02:00 p.m. to 03:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:Sarovar\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
\nWelcome to the event SAE 2015 to spread your innovative ideas, way of presenting skills and mechanical skills.
\nImagination is not only the unique human capacity to envision that which is not, and, therefore, the foundation of all invention and innovation. In its arguably most transformative and revelatory capacity, it is the power that enables us to empathize with humans whose experiences we have never shared. So, warm up your body to show your mechanical skill and designing depth by making your own wooden car.
\nFrom the moment "GO" begins the race and all throughout you keep dreaming of just one place, the finish line. Gripping the ground and raising the gear you keep moving but finally comes the fear and apart from winning you just don’t care. When your car hits the race let the track itself say, oh!! Here comes the one that shall show you the way.
\nAnd yes, the winner takes it all, because we don’t believe in speed limits and restraint.
\n

\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nDivyank Dubey
\ndivyank98@gmail.com
8506949419</b>
</string>
    <string name="boatwars"><b>\nBOAT WARS\n
\n\n\nTime:01:00 p.m. to 03:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue:Sarovar\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n</b>
\nThis is a competition for undergraduate and graduate students where teams have to design and fabricate an RC Controlled Motor driven boat .The vehicle must be aerodynamic, highly engineered and ergonomically designed.
\nRULES and REGULATIONS
\n•	Prelims will be held on February 04th , 2015 .
\n•	Virtual round:

\nTeams will be asked to give a detailed presentation of their boat layout. The PPT consists of every kind of Technical details, hand sketches, cost approximation and reason for selection of their particular design.
\n.
\n\n\n\nCONTACT
\nMahendra Pratap Singh
\nmahendralmp@gmail.com
08377866402
</string>
    <string name="palaceofcards"><b>\nPALACE OF CARDS\n
\n\n\n\nTime:11:00 a.m. to 12:00 p.m. on February 14th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\nVenue:SOE Backside\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
\nA Palace of cards is a structure created by stacking playing cards on top of each other. This event is organized to provide the students a chance of facing the types of connections between the cards that is look like a truss structure. The structures created, using this method relies on nothing more than balance and friction in order to stay upright. Ideally, adhesives or other external connecting methods are not used. Your job is to represent the number of story by placing minimum cards together in a specific manner.
\n

\n\n\n\CONTACT
\nSatya Prakash Singh
\n11/ICE/093
satyagbu93@gmail.com
8860872348</b>
</string>
    <string name="brickbond007"><b>\nBRICK BOND 007</b>\n
\n\n\n<b>Time:03:30 p.m.-04:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\n\nVenue:Sarovar\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION\n
\nA bond is something that binds or restrains the members so that they don’t part off. It is not only important between the people but also plays a vital role in aspects of civil engineering. This event is organized to provide the students a chance of facing the types of connections between the bricks that are being used in every step of civil engineering and there difference in terms of strength, aesthetic.
\n
\nCONTACT
\nShubham Singh
\n11/ICE/102
theknight279@gmail.com\n
7838916117</b>
</string>
    <string name="creativewriting">\nC<b>REATIVE WRITING\n
\n\n\nTime : 2:00 p.m. to 3:30 p.m. on February 13th , 2015\n
\n\n\nVenue : SOM Lecture Room\n
\n\n\nDESCRIPTION,\n
\n•  IT INCLUDES TWO SEPARATE EVENTS
\na)”DEKHO PARKHO AUR BOLO” (picture description)
\nb)SLOGAN WRITING
\nRULES and REGULATIONS
\na) ”DEKHO PARKHO AUR BOLO” (picture description)
\n\n\n\n<u>GENERAL GUIDELINES</u>
\n• A picture will be displayed to everyone
\n• One has two describe it in his/her own way whether prose or poetry
\n• Each participant will be provided 45 min
\n• Participant can prefer any language Hindi /English/Urdu
\n• A4 sheets will be provided to every one for his/her own picture description
\nb) SLOGAN WRITING
\n\n\n\n<u>GUIDELINES</u>
\n• Topic will be provided on the spot (common for every participant)
\n• 15 min will be provided to write the slogan in word limit of 30 words
\n• Participant can prefer any language hindi /English
\n• A4 sheets will be provided which participants have to submit later
\nCONTACT
\nNivesh Singh : niveshsingh007@gmail.com
\n9650477491</b>
</string>
    <string name="credits"><b>Credits: PARENTS ,TEACHERS and FRIENDS</b>\n
If the heavens were all parchment and the trees of the forest all pens,and every human being were a scribe,it would be impossible to record all that we have learned from our PARENTS,TEACHERS and FRIENDS\n\n\n

</string>

</resources>
